

Kaj Printz MADSEN Aalborg/Denmark +45 31429433 kajprintz@gmail.com

github in linkedin

PROFILE

Kaj is a full-stack developer with extensive experience in modern web development and a strong passion for developing high-quality, mission-critical software.

Kaj has 3 years of experience with cloud & CI/CD technologies, including AWS & Azure, which makes him wellacquainted with the full lifecycle of a program from coding to testing, implementation, and maintenance. He has extensive experience with agile development methods and is accustomed to consulting with clients on solution descriptions, thanks to his experience as a consultant.

EDUCATION

MSc. SOFTWARE 2016-2018

· Master of Science - Software, Aalborg University

BSc. Software 2013-2016

Bachelor of Science - Software, Aalborg University

PROJECT EXPERIENCE

NETCOMPANY - CONSULTANT AT AUTOPROFF A/S

2022- i dag

As a member of the AI team, I developed backend infrastructure in Python to support our AI team. My responsibilities included building and maintaining REST APIs, and developing new services deployed on Amazon Web Services. In addition to my work in Python, I also contributed to the development of the company's PHP-based backend systems. I collaborated with the frontend team to ensure seamless integration of the backend and frontend components of our applications.

TECHNOLOGIES: PYTHON, PHP, C#., NET, ASP, NET, TERRAFORM, AWS, GITHUB ACTIONS, DOCKER, LINUX

CEGO A/S - SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

2020-2022

Developed and designed a solution for live updating of website content via websockets. Utilized PHP backend and incorporated user feedback to fix errors and improve website functionality. Strong problem-solving skills and ability to create effective solutions for web development gained through this experience.

TECHNOLOGIES: WEBSOCKET, LARAVEL, PHP, GITLAB CI/CD,

DEPARTMENT OF GENOMIC MEDICINE RIGSHOSPITALET - SOFTWARE DEVELOPER2018-2020
Developed a platform for tracking and record keeping of patients' blood sample tests on a trial basis using Python and Django as the backend technology.

TECHNOLOGIES: PYTHON, JAVASCRIPT, PHP, REDHAT SERVER

CERTIFICATIONS

CISCO PYTHON ESSENTIALS - PCEP MICROSOFT AZURE - AZ900 AWS CERTIFIED CLOUD PRACTITIONER - CLF-C01 Issued Dec 2022

Issued Nov 2022

Issued Oct 2022

SKILLS

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGE Python | PHP | C# | Javascript | Typescript | Java | Bash

GIT | CLI | Devops | Agile Development Method SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT

Amazon Web Services | Azure | Docker | Terraform | SQL | GNU/Linux **PLATFORMS & FRAMEWORKS**

> Native Language: Danish Fluent: English LANGUAGE

January 8, 2023